- Tonight on
"The Bachelorette"...
- Whoo!
- We're here in Crete,
Greece and...
♪ It's Fantasy Suite Week ♪
- There's no more secret.
I am in love with Hannah.
This is what I want
for the rest of my life.
It's so surreal
and it's so exciting
to be on the same page.
I know that she knows
that I'm--I'm the one.
[kissing]
- Physical intimacy with Tyler
is not an issue.
Holding me and kissing me--
I just want that.
But, like, it has to be more.
Like, I don't want
to go into Fantasy Suite.
- I need some clarity on Luke
because I would be completely
lying to you if I said it
didn't affect the way I feel.
And when I feel worried,
I feel like I retract
how I feel.
- So let's talk about sex,
and let's say you have had sex
with one or multiple
of these guys.
I'd completely remove myself
from this relationship.
- Oh, my God, I cannot believe
you just said that.
I'm so mad.
I don't owe you anything
at this point.
My husband would never say
what you said to me.
From--from obviously
how you feel,
me [bleep] in a windmill,
probably...
you probably want to leave.
- [groans]
[tense music]
- It's all coming up tonight
on "The Bachelorette."
[folk music]
♪ ♪
- This week we're here
in Crete, Greece,
and it is absolutely
breathtaking.
It is so dreamy.
There's so much culture
and history here...
cobblestone streets
and beautiful buildings.
Magical blue waters.
So romantic.
I mean, it is a dream place
to fall in love.
Especially because
♪ It's Fantasy Suite week ♪
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
I can't believe that, like,
the end of my journey here
is very close.
After hometowns last week,
I really could see myself
being ready for an engagement
to any of the four men here.
♪ ♪
It has been a long time since
I've been physical at all
with a man,
but Fantasy Suite Week
is not about sex.
It's to have the time
in a real raw way
without cameras
to see where
my feelings are truly
and really find out, like,
who I want to be with
for the rest of my life.
♪ ♪
Out of the four guys left,
Peter and I had a slower start
but we've definitely had
a strong connection
since our relationship
really took off.
He is that nice guy
that you feel
that you can
bring him anywhere.
He has his life together
but he also is still
really passionate
and there's something
really sexy about him.
And if all goes well,
guess what.
♪ Gonna get down ♪
Bow-dah-bow!
Ow!
♪ In the Fantasy Suite ♪
- Hello!
- Hey!
- We in Greece!
[both laughing]
Oh, my God.
Come here.
Oh!
♪ ♪
I missed you.
This is insane.
Like, this is the most
beautiful place I've ever seen.
- I know.
- Unreal.
- I'm so excited to be here.
- Whoo, can't wait!
- Um, so...I'm really excited
to check out
these beautiful waters with you
in a really cool way.
- All right.
- See that boat over there?
- Yeah.
- I think we're gonna
sail on it today.
- Is that our ride?
Oh, my God.
Yes.
- [laughs]
[mellow music]
- Here we go.
[boat engine running]
This is literally a dream.
This is not real life.
- Oh, my gosh!
[laughs]
- Oh, my God.
Whoo!
- Oh, my gosh!
- [laughs]
This is amazing.
Hannah and I, we just have
a very special connection.
We've always had that passion
and that's been undeniable
since the beginning.
But more than that, like,
whew!
I'm getting all jittery just,
like, talking about it,
but yeah, she's, like--
she has my heart.
Oh, my God, Hannah.
Look at that.
Are you kidding me?
Hannah and I would have the
most fun life ever together.
That's what I've
been looking for,
someone to travel with
and experience new things
and it's just the taste of,
like,
what our life would be like.
Honestly, I don't know if I
like kissing you on a plane
or a boat better.
[both laughing]
I've stripped down every wall
that I ever had.
I've never been this, like,
exposed to someone.
Like, just this
totally raw someone.
If I could get a picture
with you in this,
like, background...wow.
That'd be, like, my screensaver
on my phone forever.
Like, I would never change it.
I haven't been completely
vocal to Hannah
how much she means to me.
There's so many moments where
I kinda just wanna, like,
get up and scream, like,
how I feel about her.
Just, like, let it all out.
Let those feelings and emotions
just straight from the heart
just, like, spill out.
I'm the king of the world!
- And I'm the queen!
- Whoo!
- [laughs]
Damn.
This is a dream.
- [softly] I know.
- Yeah.
I love this and I'm so
grateful for everything
and how it's worked out.
It's crazy how, like,
real this is getting.
- Yeah.
- This is, like, it,
you know?
- It is real.
It's, like, scary but good.
- I think just 'cause I know
what this means
and, I dunno, it's just
kinda like hitting me.
[kisses]
Do you know how much
I like you?
- I hope a lot.
- You have no idea.
You're the most beautiful girl
in the world.
Sailing the Mediterranean.
- It's perfect.
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
Peter's so sexy
and so great and so sweet.
It's the total package of,
like, what I always dreamed
I would be with.
[clanging]
[both laughing]
- We're the worst
deckhands ever.
♪ ♪
- But there's still, like,
a layer of him holding back
a little bit.
He said, "You have no idea
how much I like you."
But I want to know that the guy
that I choose at the end
of this is--
does love me.
I think tonight's really,
really important,
not just that
it's Fantasy Suite
but that, like,
I just need to hear more
of where he's at.
I guess I'll see if it's
going to be smooth sailing
or rocky waters.
- Oh, my goodness.
[mellow folk music]
♪ ♪
- Hello.
- Wow.
- [laughs]
- You look beautiful.
- Aww.
- Oh, my God.
- [laughs]
- Just seeing Hannah, like,
I had to pinch myself.
Like, how did I get so lucky
just to meet
this amazing person with such
a beautiful soul and heart?
I truly feel like we're--
we're meant for each other.
But it's been such a long time
for me to truly express
love for someone else,
and that part...
honestly, is, like,
terrifying to me.
Wow, look at this.
- Isn't this beautiful?
- Stunning.
This is also getting
so down to the wire.
Like, I've gotta let
her know how I feel.
Like, I--I can't lose Hannah
at this point.
Like, I've never met someone
anywhere close to the type
of person that she is.
Like...
♪ ♪
[exhales]
Damn.
Well, cheers to love
and to fate
bringing us together,
having no idea, like,
where we'd end up
from that first night.
- Mm-hmm.
- But I've just truly,
truly enjoyed every single
moment I spent with you.
- Me, too.
- So we say to that
stin ygeiá sas.
- Stin ygeiá sas.
- That's cheers in Greek.
- Really?
- Yeah, I just learned it.
- Cheers!
- Stin ygeiá sas.
- [laughs]
I need to take this off.
I'm actually now sweating.
- Getting a little hot?
- Okay.
- Yeah, today was...
it was so beautiful.
And honestly, like, for me,
every moment, like,
from the beginning
of this journey
has been a dream for me.
I feel like our relationship
has just, like,
very solidly progressed.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know, like, every week...
- Yeah.
- It's been, like, a new step
and a new jump
and just getting stronger
and stronger.
- And that's really
important here.
- And that's--yeah.
- Yeah.
It's a good sign for me, too.
- Sure.
I totally feel the same.
[sighs]
Yeah.
This is, um...
So, going back
to hometowns last week,
it's like the reaction,
you know,
from my family and just them,
like, totally accepting you
and I've been so invested.
- Me, too.
- Now I feel like they're
invested, too, now.
And I remember leaving that day
just, like, feeling so good
at where we're at and, like,
where we can go.
- Mm-hmm.
- And...
I, um...
So when we were flying...
- Yeah?
- Um, obviously you know
how much I love flying.
- Yeah.
- Right?
But flying with you was like
a whole new experience
that I had never had.
- Really?
- And I had never felt
anything like that before.
And just--it was kinda like
everything hitting me, like,
how strongly I feel.
And, uh...
It was weird.
Honestly, like, today...
- Mm-hmm.
- I was, like, really nervous.
- Why?
- And I know, like,
it makes no sense
'cause I loved today.
It was so beautiful.
But, like, the entire time--
- It was hard.
- It was hard and, like,
I was--
- I kinda--Like--
it's like...
I'm scared--I get, like,
nervous about all this.
It's...hard and magical
and amazing
at the same time, so...
- I guess trying to explain
to you why this
is such a big deal for me and,
like, the nerves and all that,
I, you know,
with previous stuff,
have not made, like,
the best decisions.
Like, women that maybe
I thought
like I had to be perfect
in those relationships,
and it wasn't, like,
my true self.
- Mm-hmm.
- And meeting you,
it was completely opposite.
- It's like not at all
what I want, yeah.
- And I've never
had someone like you
ever in my life, Hannah.
Like, you truly, like--
you inspire me.
Like, you--you push me.
Like, you challenge me.
And so I know what
I have with you.
The flaws, the great things,
like, I just--
the way you are, like,
it's perfect for me.
- My moodiness?
- The moodiness is fine.
No, I can put up with that.
Like, 'cause I can be moody.
And maybe I haven't
shown it yet, but...
you just--the way you make
me feel so comfortable
to be my true self,
I have just never truly
felt like that for someone
until I met you.
And it, uh...it made me...
it made me realize...
[soft, emotional music]
♪ ♪
How in love with you I am.
And it's the greatest
feeling ever.
♪ ♪
- Whoo!
- [laughs]
- Yay!
- It feels...amazing.
- It wasn't that bad to say,
was it?
- It's--no,
it's--it's--it's--
You don't know how much
that means, though,
to say that.
Like, honestly.
[sighs]
And the way you make me feel,
I just--I want this feeling
every day.
I love Hannah.
- [laughs]
Yes.
♪ ♪
- When Peter said
that he loves me,
I was just like--
melts my heart.
And it was sweet because of,
like, the anticipation,
how nervous he was,
and so it was just so, like,
nice to just finally hear
the words from him.
[both laughing]
♪ ♪
Well...
- Oh!
- I have this...
- Hello.
- Note that I just...
- Where'd that come from?
- I don't know, it just--
- You really don't want
the night to end.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- So I want you to read this.
- Okay.
I would love to.
What's in here?
"Hannah and Peter,
"welcome to the beautiful
island of Crete.
"I hope you both enjoyed
your day cruising
"the crystal blue waters
of the Aegean Sea.
"Should you choose to forego
your individual rooms,
"please use this key
to stay as a couple
"in the Fantasy Suite.
Chris Harrison."
[laughs]
Well, thanks, Chris.
- Truly, though, like,
I think it's really important
to have...more time.
Like, I need it.
- Yeah.
- I don't know how you feel.
- I totally do.
- But, like, I just need that.
- I'm all in if you're in.
- I'm in.
- All right, let's do it.
[kisses]
Guess what?
- Yeah?
- I love you.
- [laughs]
- All right, let's go.
It feels so good being 100%,
like, transparent
of how I feel.
And so I am the happiest
person in the world,
and this definitely
I feel like could be
one of the best nights
in my life.
Wow.
- That's so cool.
- That's beautiful.
Greece is known
for their windmills, right?
- Sure.
- I think so.
Look at this.
♪ ♪
Wow!
- [laughs]
- That is so cool.
- Aww!
How cool!
- No way.
- Like, it's legit a windmill.
- We are literally staying
in a windmill.
- We're in a windmill.
This is my first Fantasy Suite.
Um, a little nervous.
Oh, it's like a little loft.
- A little loft up there?
Oh, my God.
- Having private time together
doesn't just grow
the relationship physically
but emotionally,
and that's so important.
[gasps]
Oh, my God.
- Oh. Some goodies there?
- Peter!
- Okay, that was
not me this time.
We're gonna close that--Stop--
- Did you put this in there?
- Not me.
[laughs]
- I don't have
any expectations,
but intimacy is really
important to me
and something that
I hold dear in my heart.
It's important to have those
moments where I can be like
my body is your body,
my heart is your heart,
my soul--like, we are
completely entangled
in every single way.
That's what I, like, know
that I want from my future.
- Oh, I could get used to this.
[laughs]
- [blows]
- Good call.
- [laughs]
- Coming up...
- Physical intimacy with Tyler
is not an issue.
Holding me and kissing me,
I just want that.
But, like, it has to be more.
Like, I don't want
to go into Fantasy Suite.
- And later...
- I need some clarity on Luke.
- Mm-hmm.
- The only thing that I need
to understand is why.
- [clears throat]
Um, like, how honest
do you want me to be?
[birds chirping]
[buzzing]
[waves rushing]
- That was such
an amazing night.
- Mmm.
Waking up with Peter
this morning,
I feel amazing.
Oh, he's so, like, loving
and passionate.
It was really great and, yeah,
it feels really nice.
- I'm feeling so good.
- Me, too.
If Peter was a Greek god,
he would be Zeus.
And then I'd be, like,
Aphrodite,
the Greek goddess of love.
[upbeat folk music]
♪ ♪
[laughs]
- I feel so confident
in what we have now.
I love you.
♪ ♪
Now let's get some breakfast.
Last night was the best night
of my life.
We came together, like,
so much last night.
Just bonded.
Just such a great feeling.
I do have that sense that,
like, we are one now.
- Cheers.
I could definitely
get used to waking up
next to you every morning.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, definitely.
That was so good.
Especially, like,
after last night,
I think that we can
for sure agree
that we took our relationship
to the next level.
- Mm-hmm.
- This is so real.
- I know.
- Like, this is it,
but I'm here
and I'll be patient.
But I don't want
to say bye to you.
[soft guitar music]
♪ ♪
There's no more secret.
I am in love with Hannah.
And I love it.
It's gonna definitely be tough
to be away from Hannah.
But I'm just gonna keep
thinking about the times
we spent together
and keep replaying those things
in my mind and it doesn't
bother me, like,
about the other guys.
Mmm...
It'd be really tough
for me to imagine her
having something this special
with someone else.
I just feel so secure
in what we have
and after last night,
I'm just like,
mic drop.
Game over.
Hannah's mine.
[laughs]
[energetic music]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
[laughs]
- What's up?
I've missed you, girl.
- I've missed you.
- Oh.
- Whoo!
[both laughing]
- How are you?
You look so pretty.
I'm so excited to see my girl.
I feel like since hometowns
I don't really have
any questions or worries
or doubts no more.
I'm just ready to propose
and get down on one knee
and be her man.
- You look great.
- You look amazing.
- Thank you.
- Nice little tan
you got going on.
- Hey, I'm in Greece.
- I know.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
- It is.
Hey.
Um, today we are going
to indulge and relax.
I feel like we deserve it,
and I can't wait.
So let's get started.
- Let's do it.
Come here.
That's what I need.
- I do, too.
- That's what I need.
[soft music]
You look absolutely amazing.
- Aww, thank you.
Tyler keeps surprising me,
and I never thought
we would be at this point.
Our physical chemistry
has been powerful
and we've had a great,
easy, fun relationship
and I've been able
to relax with him,
So it's a totally
different dynamic
than any other
relationship here.
- Hi, Hannah, Tyler.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
May I please escort you into
our mini spa relaxation area?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Yes, please.
- Thank you.
Please follow me.
- This girl loves to indulge,
so she's ready.
- He truly is not just like
this Greek god of a man.
Like, he is so sweet
and so kind.
Just fun to be with.
- Please take off
your bathrobes,
if you wish,
and lie on the bed
with face up.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- Whew! Girl!
- [laughs]
- Oh, my gosh.
[laughs]
- You can come on this side.
- That blue
is a very nice color.
- Thanks.
- There we go.
That's what I'm talking about.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- Jupiter was awesome.
- It was really fun.
It was great meeting
everybody and--
- Yeah, they loved you.
- Yeah?
- Miss Hannah B.
- I had the best time.
- I see a little
Florida girl in there.
- Oh, I was loving it.
I had the best time
obviously with you,
but then I was like,
"Okay, I like Jupiter.
This is nice."
- Yeah?
My dad, how'd it go
with him and you?
- He was just, like,
surprised with you.
And that's what he, like--
we talked about.
He was like, "I'm scared."
And I was like, "Me, too."
[both laughing]
All of your family, like,
they were just
so welcoming to me.
- Yeah, my mom loved you and--
- She was really sweet.
- Yeah.
- Your brothers,
I was like,
"These are like my people."
- Really?
- Just so fun, yeah.
- That's awesome.
I could see that--
I could see you guys
getting along,
but then I was like--
it felt like it clicked.
You know?
- Mm-hmm.
- Like you belonged.
- It's time to start the
treatment with the body wrap.
- All right.
- Okay, cool.
Tyler is that dream guy
that every woman
has wanted to be with.
And I'm like,
"Whoa...
he wants to be with me?"
- You're making it hard for me
to relax, Hannah.
I wanna pounce on that table.
- You're making me blush, okay?
- Mmm.
♪ ♪
- I was like,
"That's not the same hands."
- [laughing]
- Who could be...
Tyler...
- Huh?
- You're...
- You what?
- You're just making me blush.
- It's okay.
Blushing's good.
Plus, your masseuse can't do
one of these to you, you know?
- I can't move.
- Stay where you're at.
♪ ♪
- I'm 1,000% sure that
physical intimacy with Tyler
is not an issue.
When I'm with him,
I'm with him.
And being with him
is very sexy
and hot and steamy
because he, like, tempts me
and I want to be
physical with him.
♪ ♪
But I feel nervous
and scared about just how far
our physical connection
can go when our
emotional communication
needs to catch up sometimes.
- Yes, it is.
If Tyler's my forever,
then I have forever
to be physical with him.
I need to make sure
that he's my forever.
[both chuckling]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Hello.
- How's my beautiful girl?
- [laughs]
I'm good.
How are you?
- I'm so much better now.
- [laughs]
- I'm on top of the world.
Today was very intimate
and just so nice.
Did you have fun today?
- I had the best time today.
- That was amazing.
- [laughs]
- I'm not sure what Hannah's
feeling tonight,
but this could possibly
lead to the Fantasy Suite
and, you know,
that's an amazing opportunity
for us to grow even more.
Keep fueling that fire
that we share between us.
- Ooh, this is so pretty.
- Wow.
I'm gonna look
into her eyes tonight
and kiss her and hold her,
and there's no reason
to hold back right now.
I want to give her all of me,
everything I got.
There's gonna be fireworks.
It's gonna be the most
amazing night in Crete.
Today was so much fun.
- It was really fun.
You have another career
under your belt.
- Yeah, you know.
- Especially with
your shirt off--that helps.
- Ooh, okay.
- [laughing]
- And how many masseuses
get to kiss you, you know?
- Yeah.
- A little extra.
- Yeah, it was--it was nice.
- What I love about today
and kind of the thing
with all of our dates,
it's been, like,
things that we are so good at.
Like, the simple things.
Everything we've done
has, like, been so easy.
- Well, that's been really
important to me
with all the dates
that we've had,
that we can still do that
and--and really be able
to picture a life
with this person.
- Yeah.
It's just for me it gives me
so much hope and excitement.
- Mm-hmm.
- And our future is close
and it's getting real.
- Yeah.
- I just embrace it
and, like, I love it and, like,
I want to run with this
and see wherever
life takes us,
'cause I'm on top of the world
right now with you.
- I feel like our relationship
has been so fun,
so easy,
and I'm so excited
to continue growing
in our emotional relationship
and communicating and getting
to know each other in that way.
But, um,
there is a concern for me
about our physical
relationship.
- Yeah?
- It is a huge part
of our relationship.
I just am so captivated
about being around you
and you holding me and kissing
me--like, I just want that.
Like, I do,
and so I have to kind of
reset myself sometimes
and think,
"Okay, like, that's great.
"You know that that's there.
But, like, it has to be more."
I...like, I don't want to go
into Fantasy Suite
and have sex because
I don't feel like
that's what our relationship
needs.
It would be very easy for me
to want to do that.
- Yeah.
- I think we have to explore
just, like, being together
and continue, like,
our emotional connection
and have that--that time.
Like, that's what we need
in a Fantasy Suite.
- You know, tonight, you know,
the Fantasy Suite and all that,
it has like
a connotation of sex.
For me, it's...
it's way more than that.
You know,
I just wanna be with you
and have that time with you,
you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- You have to really love
and respect
and honor each other's
boundaries, you know?
And, like, I would never press
you or pressure you at all.
I want you to be 100%
comfortable and confident
in whatever we do together.
And, like, I look
at the man I am today--
is not the same kid
I was nine weeks ago, you know?
And you got me
to open up so much
and I don't want this to end.
I don't wanna stop looking
in your eyes.
I don't wanna stop
seeing that smile.
hearing that laugh,
like, seeing those dimples.
Like, I could stand here today
and, like, tell you,
like, I--I do love you.
Like, I am so falling for you
and, like,
you mean the world to me
I would love to spend
more time with you
and just be us
and enjoy this night
under the stars here in Greece
and, you know,
a night that we'll cherish
and remember forever.
What about you?
- Me, too.
- Awesome.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- I think he handled what
I said really well tonight.
He didn't question
why I felt the way I did.
It didn't faze him.
Let's go have a night.
- Let's have a night.
- By ourselves.
- And a morning.
- Yeah.
[laughs]
It shows how much he loves me.
- Wow, this is
a beautiful boat.
- It is so pretty.
I feel really good about going
into a Fantasy Suite with him
and just being res--respected.
[cork pops]
Whoo!
He makes me feel strong
because he allows me to be
the strong woman that I am and
he celebrates my boundaries.
- To a night on this lovely
boat with the woman I love
and cherish and want to spend
the rest of my life with.
- Cheers.
♪ ♪
[mellow music]
[seagull squawking]
[waves rolling]
♪ ♪
- This really is really pretty.
- It's a beautiful day.
- What a day.
What a morning.
- What a morning.
This was the most
amazing night.
- It was.
- It was beautiful.
- You're nice to wake up to.
You're even good
to look at in the morning.
Some people aren't.
You're just like this.
- That's just like you.
Look at you right now.
- Mmm.
- Gorgeous, girl.
I guess I could wake up
to this all the time.
I want you to be the last
person I wake up to.
Forever.
- I'm really grateful for you
being so respectful
of the boundaries
that I wanted to put
on our relationship last night.
- But it was what we needed.
- Yeah.
Still great to just be,
like, held and kissed,
but, like, you did not allow it
to go further,
and there's a time for that.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I just--it's probably
the hottest thing, honestly.
Probably made me want
to do it more,
but, like--
- Of course.
Like, I want things
to be organic and happen
the way you want them
to happen.
I want it to be natural,
you know?
We just have to be us
and let it come easy
and natural like we have
this whole relationship.
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
It was one of the best nights
of my life.
We just sat there
and hung out
and just talked and talked.
Like, this is love.
This is so real.
Like, that's gonna be my girl.
That's gonna be my best friend.
That's gonna be my wife.
It just seems to fit so easily
and perfectly.
It was meant to happen.
Feel like the luckiest man
in the world.
This is, like,
the hardest good-bye.
- I know.
It is for me, too.
♪ ♪
I had a really great night
with Tyler.
We would make out,
and he would stop.
And just hold me.
And--and be like,
"This is the best night ever."
- I love you.
- [groans]
He was the most respectful man
that's ever been with me.
♪ ♪
Ever.
- I love you.
- Bye.
He continues to show me
more and more of who he is.
I figured out a whole 'nother
part of him
that I've put blinders onto.
And, like, watching him just
leave me from our date
like, it ripped me.
- [blows kiss]
- I really need to just,
like, think and process
all my relationships.
Like, it makes me, like,
really emotional.
♪ ♪
It's really hard.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- I need some clarity on Luke.
- What you're basically
saying to me is, like,
I don't know how you can
have feelings for me
and have feelings for him.
I'm really frustrated.
[groans]
Uggghhh!
I do not want
to do this anymore.
- And later...
- Let's say you have
had sex with one
or multiple of these guys.
I'd completely remove myself
from this relationship.
- You don't own me.
You don't get to decide
what I can and can't do.
My husband would never say
what you said to me.
[uplifting music]
[dog barking]
[engine revving]
♪ ♪
- Today's really important
for me because
last time I saw Hannah
I honestly felt pretty angry.
I felt let down.
♪ ♪
Coming off that
last Rose Ceremony,
it was just hurtful
to stand there next to Luke
and feel like it was between me
and this person
who has been so inconsistent
and toxic.
In my mind and my heart,
I feel like there's
no comparison
and it doesn't make
any sense to me.
♪ ♪
But I don't want to let someone
else affect our relationship
because today's a huge day.
Here I am angry with a girl
that I've fallen in love with.
I want nothing more than
to just focus all my energy
on her and fall in love
even deeper in Greece.
- Hey.
- Hello.
♪ ♪
How are you?
- Hey.
Good now.
How are you?
- I missed you.
I'm good.
You look beautiful.
- Oh, thank you.
You look handsome.
- I like your dress.
Ooh.
- Thanks.
Welcome.
- Thank you.
- I have a great day planned in
this cute little Greek village.
[cat meows]
Oh! Kitties.
[both laughing]
So we're gonna
take in the culture.
- I'm excited.
I missed you.
- I missed you.
Ready?
- Let's do it.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[man speaking in native
language]
- Greece is known for
the simple pleasures in life--
food, sunshine,
time spent with family.
So we're gonna get
a little help
from an expert in that today.
Hello.
- Welcome.
- It's so nice that
this family gathering
allowed Jed and I
to be a part of it.
♪ ♪
I'm really excited about
this date today with Jed.
It's like we didn't
just go to Greece.
We experienced Greece
the way that
the people that live there do.
♪ ♪
[whistling, clapping]
The last time that I saw
Jed at his hometown,
he told me that he loved me.
I am falling in love with Jed,
and he's the only guy
that I've even verbally
said that to.
I can see a life with Jed.
But it's like today's date,
tonight, everything, like,
would solidify that
if it went well.
♪ ♪
- Bravo, bravo!
[all speaking in Greek]
- What the hell?
- Jed.
- Yannis.
- Nice to meet you.
- That was not water!
[all laughing]
Ah! That was not water!
- This is a typical Greek...
Viagra.
- Wait, what did you say?
Viagra?
- Viagra?
Ooh!
- Really?
- Very nice.
- Thinking about it, yeah.
- Very nice, very nice.
- Ooh.
- Oh, I'm not--I
don't know just yet.
- Almost ready.
Oh, no.
I am not ready to make
a decision just yet.
This week is really
important to me.
I get more time with
the four men that I'm dating.
And I want to be
really positive
in all my relationships.
Um...
[clears throat]
Put me on the spot.
[dramatic music]
I think you fall in love
in different ways
and relationships have,
um, different ways
of, like, growing.
So I just need clarity.
I want to know that
at the end of this
that I can look at somebody
in the eye
and know that I want to spend
forever with them, so--
- You want to be sure.
- I want to be 1,000% sure.
So I'm just trying to figure
that out right now.
- You think--you think
from the first look?
- Yeah.
[sighs]
- It's hard, though.
Like, you have to...
you have to, like,
really listen to your heart.
Like, I'm not battling a bunch
of different relationships,
but it's like the idea
of the person
that I'm falling in love with
being with other people,
that's tou--it's hard.
♪ ♪
- Yeah.
- Come here.
- About what?
Talk to me.
- I just need to talk to you.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- Huh?
Hey, your fa--
you're scaring me.
- No, don't be scared.
- Oh, okay.
- Don't be scared.
- Okay.
- Um, so I feel like something
has just weighed on my heart
for a long time now.
- Mm-hmm.
- Because I'm in this for you,
and I've fallen for you.
And especially at this point
it's just, like,
it's so serious at this point
that, like,
I need some clarity on Luke.
- Mm-hmm.
- It doesn't add up to me
just because I know you now.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I care about you a lot.
And I don't wanna see you hurt.
And I wanna see you be with
the best person
that you can be with.
And I've seen Luke
from the beginning
take people's words
and change them.
I've seen him lie.
I just don't fully understand
how you can be
as amazing as you are and even
consider someone like him.
- [clears throat]
Um...
I don't wanna say anyth--
Like, how honest
do you want me to be?
- I--
- L--like, I don't wanna--
Like I--I'm--
[clears throat]
From--at the beginning,
we had a, like--
like, I had a really, like,
strong connection with him
that I couldn't
really describe.
Like, I always have said, like,
it was just--it was weird.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, he definitely
grabbed my attention first
because it was very obvious
to me that he's here for me.
I met his family.
I do think he's here for me.
And...there is a connection.
- Mmm.
- But I'm still trying
to figure it out.
I do think he's a good guy.
[groans]
I don't know what to say.
Um--
- I just--
[clears throat]
I guess if...
[dramatic music]
You're this close to being
with somebody forever,
if you're this close
to finding your husband,
then what makes you hold on
to something so uncertain?
♪ ♪
- Um, a feeling.
Our relationship's
a little bit different.
It--I've seen
different sides of him
that I know
that y'all haven't seen.
- Gotcha.
Okay.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- Thank you
for saying something.
- Okay.
I'm so upset.
I really care about Hannah.
I've told Hannah
that I love her.
I don't want to see her give
her attention to someone
who I feel could
potentially hurt her.
- You gotta let me...
figure it out.
- I thought she was gonna see
right through his [bleep].
But the fact that
he's still here,
it just scares me.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
- Earlier today,
Jed was really concerned
and thinking a lot about
his frustrations with Luke
and his frustrations about
Luke and I's relationship.
I get it.
I understand.
But I think it's important
to just reiterate to him
that my decisions
with that relationship
has no effect
on how I feel about him.
- Whoo-hoo.
- [laughs]
- You look great.
- This ole thing?
- Oh, my gosh.
You look beautiful.
- I think it was really
coming from a place
of, like, he loves me,
he really cares about me.
- Wow.
Look at all of these trees.
- Yeah.
- Let's take your jacket off.
- Thank you.
But trust is like
the number one thing
I think a relationship
has to be built on.
Hopefully,
we've moved past it.
Um...
cheers to
being able to be honest
and share our feelings,
even when it's hard.
And then also
just having a fun day
in a culture
with new friends and family.
[laughs]
- Cheers.
[glasses clink]
On that note, um,
I wanted to start off tonight
by saying thank you and that
I actually do appreciate
the conversation
that you pulled me aside for.
That could have been scary
and you might have
been concerned,
like, how I'd react.
And I know in the past, like,
it's pissed me off
when people have just brought
up anything with other men,
but I know
how you feel about me,
and I see it
as coming from a good place.
I don't think you're concerned
with him in any way, like,
other than you're concerned
for me and my heart.
And I've been
in the same position,
had the same conversation.
I know exactly how you feel.
But honestly, you just have to
let me figure it out.
And I feel like today was just
a really good conversation
for me to at least know
that you care.
- Yeah.
No, I totally get that.
And it was good to kind of
get the air cleared.
I--But thank you so much
for hearing me out
and, you know, with letting me
know that you did hear me,
because it's kind of like--
obviously it was a big deal
for me to bring up.
I just haven't felt a need to.
- Okay.
We good?
- Well, the thing is--
[clears throat]
The--well, the thing is that
though your and his
relationship
has nothing to do with me,
and mine and your relationship
has nothing to do with him,
but choices have to do with us.
- Mm-hmm.
- And, you know,
I would be
completely lying to you
if I said it doesn't affect
the way I feel,
and it does weigh on me,
and it's weighed on me a lot.
- Mm-hmm.
- 'Cause I know that
I've fallen in love with you.
I know that you feel similar,
so I think it's important
for you to know
where I stand with that,
especially going forward.
- I know. I know.
I'm sorry.
- What? No--
Why are you saying "sorry"?
- Because I don't want--
I don't want that affecting
how you feel about me.
- [sighs]
I guess to the core,
it kind of says a lot about
your decisions
when you can look at me
and tell me that
you're falling in love with me
but then also keep around
somebody who's been toxic
to this process for you
and everyone else.
- And how do--okay.
I get that.
Um, and okay, so that says--
And that makes you feel what?
- It makes me feel worried
that you have a hard time
letting go of things
that aren't good for you
in your life.
- Mm.
And does that make you
uncertain or--
- Uh, it causes me
to just feel, like, worried.
And when I feel worried,
I feel like
I retract how I feel.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Thanks.
Man.
- I know it's--
I know it's heavy.
- [laughs]
That was--
yeah.
I appreciate your honesty.
And--
- That's just like the--
to the root that I can go.
I don't know what else to say.
- No--I--
I feel like you hit it.
I don't want you
to go any further.
I think I'm good now.
I think that was--
- I'm just really, like,
freaking sure about you,
and I don't want to be unsure,
you know what I mean?
- [sighs]
Okay.
♪ ♪
- What's on you--
Talk to me.
- I trust you
and I trust your opinions,
but I also want you
to trust me too.
I know that's, like,
a hard thing.
What you're basically
saying to me is, like,
"I don't know how
you can have feelings for me
and have feelings for him."
And so, like, it kind of
pisses--
- I just don't want to see
the person I love
read into [bleep]
from someone like that.
- Well, I'm really frustrated.
That's what makes me mad.
Like, I just want to
get up for a second.
- [clears throat]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Hey.
- I'm just so...ugghhh!
- Just give me a hug.
Just give me a hug.
Come here.
Ugh!
I do not
want to do this anymore.
[sighs]
- I do not
want to do this anymore.
[sighs]
- Come here.
- I'm just so...ughhh!
- Just give me a hug.
Come here.
- [sniffles]
- Okay.
At dinner, I told her
the raw truth about Luke
and how it was, like, really
and truly affecting me.
And it really upset her.
I hope that it doesn't ruin
what we have
and what we share,
how amazing it is.
[sighs]
I don't know.
- [sighs]
[heavy music]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
I'm sorry.
- I know you're mad.
It's okay.
[sighs]
This comes from
a place of love in me.
This is because I--
I care about you a lot.
- I know it's frustrating.
What I'm struggling with--
with that,
I see all the things
that you're frustrated with,
and you're like,
"How is she not getting it?
"How can she
have real feelings for me
and still be having
this relationship with Luke?"
I get it.
I understand it.
But I know that, like,
the foundation of
a relationship is trust,
so if you're like,
"I don't like him"...
- Mm-hmm.
- And you care about me...
- You just have to let me
figure it out.
You know, I just want somebody
at the end of the day
that can trust
decisions I'm making.
I hear you,
and I'm thankful for you,
and by no means
is that relationship
anything to do with
the feelings
that I have for you.
But I understand
how it's frustrating.
- I just frickin' care.
Like, I really care.
I trust your decisions.
- Mm-hmm.
- I have your back.
I want to be there for you.
And I know that
whatever you choose to do
is coming from your heart,
and that's what matters to me
the most.
I know that I've fallen in love
with you.
- Mm-hmm. I know.
- And that's important to me
that you know that.
- I know.
And I appreciate that.
And I--I know it--
I know it's coming
from that place.
I--I have no questions
about that.
- Okay.
Tonight will be about us.
I love, like,
everything about you,
and I just, like,
you're just like--
[growls]
Like, you're so...
- [laughs]
- Freaking beautiful.
And, like, I just feel
this overwhelming emotion...
- Ooh!
- All the time.
Come here.
- [sighs]
- How I feel.
This isn't me trying to hurt
you in any way.
- I know.
- Okay.
- You're so great.
You're so great with me.
My conversation with Jed
freaked me out for a second,
but it really shows how much
that he cares for me
and loves me.
I'm not looking for just
a beautiful, picturesque
perfect date.
I'm looking for
real conversation,
real situations,
how do we work
through those together?
- [sighs]
- Well,
since you didn't run away,
and if you'd like to stay...
There's this card
I'd like you to read.
- [laughs]
- "Hannah and Jed,
"should you choose to forgo
your individual rooms,
"please use this key
to stay as a couple
in the Fantasy Suite."
- So what do you say?
- Let's get out of here.
- [laughing]
- Let's go.
- I feel so happy
that Hannah and I
were able to
have that conversation
and completely clear the air.
Let's go!
It just made our relationship
stronger in every way,
and I have
no doubt in my mind that
we can get through anything.
- Oh, my gosh!
- Oh!
[both laughing]
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my gosh!
- This is beautiful.
Tonight is just gonna be
such a big night
with the girl
I'm in love with.
- Oh, my God.
Look how beautiful that is.
- I just look forward
to having
that really intimate
conversation about our lives
and what we see in each other
and what we see in our future.
Because I can see myself
with her forever.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- With Jed, it's fun,
it's emotional,
it's sexy, it's honest
and sincere.
That's what you want
in a life partner.
- I'll be right back.
Our feelings for each other
are so strong.
And my soul's
invested in this.
Come to Mama.
[laughs]
- Coming up...
- I've been completely honest
with you.
I look you in the eyes...
[laughs]
I see my future wife.
This is what I want
for the rest of my life.
I'm so confident.
I know that she knows
I'm the one.
[laughs]
- Oh, my God, I cannot believe
you just said that.
I'm so mad.
I don't owe you anything
at this point.
Do you not understand that?
Oh...my God.
Who are you again?
What?
- Can I pray over you
before I leave?
- No.
[birds chirping]
[waves rushing]
- That was, like,
the best night ever.
- Mm-hmm.
It was a good night.
Fun.
- So fun.
- Sweet.
- But wild.
- And a lot of fun.
- Lot of fun.
I'm more sure than
I've ever been
about you.
- I'm more sure about you,
Mr. Jed Wyatt.
[laughs]
- I really hope that
we can wake up someday
and look back and be like,
"We did this.
We made it."
- Sounds really nice.
- I love you.
I feel like I just came off of
the best sleepover ever.
Like, you know, you're just
so happy but you're tired?
That's where I'm at.
Like, we didn't sleep a wink.
And to just
have Hannah to myself,
with no cameras, with
no one else around, just us,
was everything and more that
I could have ever dreamed for.
- I'll miss you.
- Miss you too.
I'm just, like,
super grateful that
I finally
got to have that night
and to get to open up
the way that we did.
- [whispers] Okay.
[squeals]
- Bye.
[laughs]
- It felt like a dream.
I feel really strong
going forward.
[gentle guitar music]
♪ ♪
- I can't believe
it's finally happening.
I get to spend all day
with Hannah.
I've been waiting for this
for too long.
I've had hometowns to,
you know, get on the same page
and work through things
with Hannah
and get our relationship
on the right track.
So when it comes to confidence
going into this week,
I'm so confident.
I know that she knows
I'm the one.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
Come here.
[laughs]
[laughter]
- It's good to see you.
- Mwah!
So good to see you.
[smooching]
[laughs]
Mm.
How have you been?
- Good.
It's been a long time.
- You look incredible.
Oh, my goodness.
- Thank you.
- So are we doing today?
I'm so excited.
I can't handle it.
- We're gonna have
the best day.
We're going to Santorini.
- [laughs]
Yes!
- This is bucket list:
Santorini, Greece.
So...
We're doing it?
- Let's do it.
Let's do it.
- Okay.
- [laughs]
- So we are going
to go to Santorini
on a helicopter today.
- This is crazy.
- Have you ever
been in a helicopter?
- No.
This is wild.
[helicopter engine thrumming]
You ready for this?
Let's go!
[laughs]
This is so wild.
- [laughs]
[laughing]
- Look at that ocean.
Oh, my goodness.
- Whoa.
- This view is unbelievable.
- I think it would be so fun
if we could swing from a ladder
up here.
- I love your imagination.
- I am so excited to be
on this date with Luke today.
- Wow.
- So beautiful.
It's hard to treat Luke
the same as the other
relationships here because,
frankly, he's not like
the other relationships here.
He never has been.
Ooh, I like this color blue.
- Unbelievable.
- I feel like
he's at his best with me,
when nobody else sees that.
Our hometown day was a really
good day for us.
It put things back on course,
so since then,
I feel like our relationship's
heading upward.
- Santorini's coming up.
- Oh, yeah!
- Oh...
- We're coming up to it.
- My...
Goodness.
- Ah!
Santorini!
I just know that there is
a connection between us
that is very real
and unlike anything
that I've experienced.
- Love it.
when I think of Greece,
that's what I think of
right there.
- Santorini's so romantic.
And I just am really thankful
to be here
with a guy who loves me.
- Whoo!
We made it.
- [inhales, exhales]
- This place is so beautiful.
- I'm in Santorini.
- [laughs]
Man, check this view out.
Wow.
- [gasping]
- That is breathtaking.
- [gasps]
That's like the postcard.
- Oh, my goodness.
- [gasps]
I cannot believe
I'm here right now.
- You enjoying this right now?
Enjoying this?
Checks off the bucket list.
- I know.
- Thank you for taking me.
- With Luke, I want to be
physical with him.
And he's still
the best kisser.
Oh, my God.
I don't know what
his church is teaching him,
but that boy can kiss.
- I feel like this would be an
awesome place to get married.
- It would be.
[man singing
in foreign language]
- Hey!
♪ ♪
- Oh, thank you.
- As we were dancing together,
I literally was like,
"Oh, my gosh.
Your eyes..."
And they, like,
look into my soul.
We are completely entangled
in every way.
- I'd like to make a toast
for you finding fierce love
and everything that your heart
has ever wanted.
Cheers.
- Well, I feel like at your
hometown it went really great.
It was good
to meet your family,
the people that love you
and just hear
who they believe you are.
Because I feel like I have, um,
like, I've--
I've seen that person...
- Right.
- That they've described.
And so with tonight being
such a big night,
I feel like we're starting to
enter into
a new chapter
of our relationship.
- Oh, my goodness.
[laughs]
This is unreal.
Can I just say this?
- Yeah.
- I am seriously so thankful.
Seriously.
- Thank you.
- And I've been completely
honest with you.
I look you in the eyes...
[laughs]
I see my future wife.
I don't take marriage lightly.
I don't take
dropping the L word lightly.
That's--
that's a huge deal for me.
And I know that these places
and all the picturesque views,
everything,
it's--it's been unbelievable.
But you know what?
Just--just giggling with you
and looking you in the eyes--
like, this is--
this is what I want...
- Yeah.
- For the rest of my life.
[romantic music]
♪ ♪
Hannah is just incredible--
just her presence
and everything about her.
I would not want to be
in this situation
with any other woman
in the world.
- [laughs]
- That was amazing.
I've seen a future with her
from the very beginning.
I'm just--
I'm ready for the next step.
You know,
going into next week,
I could potentially be
getting down on a knee and
asking my future wife
to marry me.
And that--that's a big deal.
And it's--it's so surreal,
and it's so exciting.
♪ ♪
[gentle music]
- Today's date
was so romantic.
Like, the most beautiful place
I could ever dream of.
- Oh, man.
- And I was just really
impressed with Luke today.
- What is up?
- [laughs]
I was like, "Whoa.
Like,
this is the guy that
I've been waiting for."
How are you?
- How are you doing?
He knows without a doubt
that he is in love with me,
and he wants me to be his wife
one day and can see that.
- Oh, look at this.
- I know.
- Oh, this is darling.
- And I feel like we're
starting to turn the page
and enter into a new chapter
of our relationship.
Um, I had so much fun today.
- That makes me so happy.
- Yeah.
- Seriously, like,
I am honored
that you chose me...
- Mm-hmm.
- To go on the date
that checks off another one of
your bucket list locations.
That's--that's a big deal.
- Yeah.
- You get so cute.
Whenever I start talking about
my feelings for you,
you, like, start
inching a little closer,
and you have,
like, laser focus.
Seriously, it's--
it's so attractive.
It made me feel really good.
- Well, I'ma make a toast.
- Yes.
- Cheers to a beautiful day
in Santorini.
- Mm.
- And being at this place
in our relationship
and where we've come from
to where we are now.
- Yes.
- Cheers.
- I'll cheers to that.
[glasses clink]
No, you're not lying.
Today was absolutely beautiful.
- Mm-hmm.
- But I'll say this.
'Cause you know,
there are things
that I do want to
talk to you about.
- Mm-hmm.
- We're talking about marriage.
This is--this is a huge deal.
- Yeah.
- And,
you know, forever
shouldn't be taken lightly.
- Yeah.
- And there's
so many things that,
you know, I want for myself
in my future wife,
my future...
- Mm-hmm.
- That, you know,
I want it the way I want it,
you know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- You brought up something
on hometowns, like,
you've been a spiritual leader
in your household.
- Uh-huh.
- That's something
that I can totally relate to.
I have been a spiritual leader
in my household.
You know how that is.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's not the easiest
all the time.
- Mm-hmm.
- But I'm so ready to, like,
make history in my family.
I want to make sure
that from now on,
things are known
how they're supposed to be.
So let's talk about sex.
- Okay.
- Um...
You know,
sex is an incredible thing.
- Mm-hmm.
- And it's a beautiful thing.
Well, only, you know,
when it's in the--
within the guidelines
of marriage.
This whole process,
I've been studying Hebrews,
and talks about how marriage
should be honored by everybody
and how the marriage bed
should be kept pure.
I know you're not a virgin.
- Mm-hmm.
- We've had the talk.
You know I'm not.
I've been abstaining myself
from sex
for, like,
3 1/2 to 4 years now...
- Mm-hmm.
- And I know that
regardless of
what I've done in the past,
I am saving myself
for marriage.
And, you know,
I am very confident
that we're on the same page
with, you know, our morals.
And I just--I want to
hear it from your mouth.
You know, like, there's
a lot of people that say
they believe in some things
but yet, like,
they live or do things
completely differently.
- Mm-hmm.
- And thinking about
Fantasy Suites,
like, I've heard people
proclaim their faith
but yet they've said things
like, you know,
"I'm excited
for Fantasy Suites.
"I want to explore
this relationship
"on a sexually intimate level,
and that's what
I'm looking forward to."
And, to me, that's, like,
"Whoa, what?"
- Mm-hmm.
- "Excuse me?"
There's something
I'm missing here.
Like, I don't believe
that's something
that you should be doing.
And I just want to make sure
you're not going to be,
you know, sexually intimate
with, you know,
the other relationships here.
- Okay.
- Like, I totally have all
the trust in the world for you.
But at the same time,
I just want to make sure
we're on the same page.
Like, if I--I mean, if I--
if you told me
you're having sex
or you had sex with
one or multiple of these guys,
I'd be wanting to go home.
- Mm-hmm.
- 100%.
- But if that's something
you're not going through,
then I'm just gonna continue
to grow the relationship
and move on.
- Um...
Like, sex is
a very big deal to me.
And I've said,
like, I've had sex
with two people in my life.
And it was long relationships
I thought were gonna be
my husband.
But some of the things
that you said,
like, I don't agree with
at all.
And honestly, like,
I'm, like, kind of mad,
because, like,
the way that
you just said that is like,
why do you
have the right to do that?
Because you're not my husband.
And you're not--
- Can I cut you off
for a second?
- No.
- Okay.
- It's just that you're--
that you're questioning me,
that you're judging me
and feel like
you have the right to
when you don't at this point.
And I get when you,
like, care for somebody
that you don't want to
think about somebody
being intimate with
another person, but guess what.
Sex might be a sin out of
marriage;
pride is a sin too.
And I feel like this is
like a pride thing.
- So...
[sighs]
I do want to take a step back
to things I have said already.
And I want you to know that...
just reassessing
what I've told you, like,
Hannah...
I don't take it lightly when
I tell you that I love you.
Let's say I am the last date.
And let's say
you have had sex--
throwing a crazy scenario
at you--
let's say you've had sex
with all these
other relationships.
All of 'em.
I--I'm willing to do or work
through anything.
You're right.
I don't have the right
to ask you that,
but to me, I just want to know
what's going on, because--
- But you did, and--
- You're right.
Because of the trust.
- Let me talk!
You did--
- You got the floor.
- You did ask.
And the words
that you just used were
will--You're "willing
to work through this."
I'm a grown woman
and can make my own decisions.
And I don't--I'm not
strapped to a man right now.
Like--
- See... [laughs]
Uh...
I don't want to get into the--
being misconstrued
and being misunderstood
thing again.
'Cause this happened a lot
with me
throughout this process.
- No, it's what you said.
- You're right, but,
to me, okay, like,
just being real, like--
- Yeah, be real.
- I can understand
a slip-up.
But, like, with all of 'em?
I mean, that's kind of where
I was going with that.
If, like, you were just like,
"You know what?
"I want to just
have sex with everyone
and see what it's like,"
then, yeah, I would be like,
"Okay...
I'ma talk to you,
but you know what?
Like, I'm out of here."
- So what would that--
- But if you had, like--
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Honestly, like,
what you're saying,
the words that you're saying
are just like really not okay.
They're just not okay.
And the closest thing
that I've ever felt to...
love at first sight
was probably with you.
And our relationship,
from the beginning,
gave me so much hope
and then it was like,
all this [bleep]...
- Yeah.
- Kept happening.
And honestly, like,
you have already
broken my heart through this,
like, truly.
And I have broken
my own heart
'cause I've allowed everything.
And...
to ignore all the red flags
for how I feel,
to have this
and to have you
say this about me
and make me feel like I--
you would look at me
any differently and judge me
or make me feel like
you would not
think of me
as a woman of faith like I am
and that we weren't
on the same page,
and it's like
you're holding your--
- I--
- No, no, no, no, no.
You're holding other people
to a standard that
you don't even live by,
maybe because
you've abstained from sex,
but there's a lot of things
that you struggle with,
and it's like because I might--
might want to or have had sex,
that's, like, your X off.
Well, like,
I could have X'd you off
so many times
from being my husband
from things that I want
out of a relationship,
and that it's just sex for you
and that you're like,
"If you've had sex,
then I'm going home."
It's like,
"Well, I want somebody
who can get along with people,
who doesn't have pride issues."
Like, there's
so many things that
I don't want out of a husband
that you've shown.
And so it's like...
Oh, my gosh.
Like...
That's a big,
like, [bleep] you.
That's what that is.
It just pissed me off.
He has said that he loves me,
and then it's like,
no, you don't
if it's so contingent on
if I fit into
what is morally acceptable
for your wife to be.
And it's like,
"[bleep] you, dude."
♪ ♪
You don't own me.
You don't get to decide
what I can and can't do.
I was like, oh...
my God.
Who are you again?
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbles]
- I guess I did say something
that I don't mean.
Because if I did find out that
one of these relationships
you did slip up
and you had sex, you know,
nothing really changes
about what I, like,
want with you
in the future still.
And--
- But I mean,
I don't slip up.
Like--
Do you--do you see this?
Like, you say that
you're so thankful to be here
and so thankful,
but you need to know
if I have had sex
with another person
for you to make the decision
of how you're going to
move forward with me.
You know
the story in the Bible
about when the woman
was caught in adultery
and she's
thrown into the village?
And Jesus is there,
and he's like,
"You without sin"...
- [muttering indistinctly]
- "Throw the first stone."
What you just did was,
you're holding your stone
up at me
and asking and trying
to see what I've done.
And...
I know that
I have God in my heart.
So I know that
everything that I do
and who I am is light.
I am light.
Do I make mistakes?
I'm not Jesus.
You've not shown respect
for any of the guys here,
and I'm finally seeing that.
And you haven't shown me
respect here,
and especially right now,
and honestly,
you haven't been
showing yourself respect here.
You keep saying,
"You should do this,
you should do that,
we should do this."
It's not a should;
it's a want.
It's a desire.
And it's not something
that you tell me that I can do;
it's that I want to do.
And
I know
that I have
given this my all.
I have cried.
I have struggled.
I have screamed.
I have made decisions
that have kept me up at night.
There have been
so many times that, like,
I have wanted to say,
"I'm done with you."
But my heart has just not
allowed me to let you go.
And I prayed so much
for clarity,
and I feel like I've finally
gotten clarity on you.
And I do not want you
to be my husband.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- Can you give me
a chance to speak?
- I don't--
No.
I--I don't--
I don't think there's--
like, I'm--I'm--
I know.
Like, I have the clarity.
Can I walk you out?
♪ ♪
- I respect
you saying
that you have clarity,
but can I still just share
a few words
with you real quick?
- Come on.
[heavy music]
♪ ♪
Come on.
It's over.
♪ ♪
[sniffles]
Luke, please, come on.
- I feel like
you owe me at least...
- I don't owe you anything.
- A minute to share...
- My heart--
- I have given you so many--
so many--Oh, my God.
I cannot believe
you just said that.
I'm so mad.
I don't owe you anything
at this point.
Do you not understand that?
I have, like,
bent over backwards
for this relationship.
So I don't owe you anything.
Please, get up.
- Can you please just
give me one minute, Hannah?
- No.
I cannot believe
you just said that to me.
- You know what--
- You don't--
No.
Walk with me.
You just--
Why would you say that?
You--I owe you?
That made me so mad.
Luke wants love for people that
only want the same thing
that he wants
and only sees things
the way that he sees love.
My husband is going to
accept me for who I am
and is gonna allow me
to be my own person.
- Me bringing those things up,
like, I--
I'm not ever judging
or condemning you.
I'm bringing up to you
what I feel like
would be the perfect scenario.
And I know that
without a shadow of a doubt--
I've never thought
if I believed
in love at first sight.
But, Hannah,
what I'm trying to tell you is,
I do love you,
and I do see a future with you,
and I know that what we had
has been completely undeniable.
I don't even care
what you just said to me
about you feeling like
you have clarity on this.
I still feel like you don't.
And there's something in me
that is refusing me
to get into that vehicle
right now, because my--
- If you really--I can probably
get you to go in that limo.
From what you said...
[laughing]
I'm like--
I'm so mad.
[laughs]
So, like, I have had sex.
- Say what?
- Yeah.
And I--Jesus still loves me.
- [groans]
- From--from obviously
how you feel,
me [bleep] in a windmill
probably--
you probably want to leave.
I didn't just
go to the Fantasy Suite.
I [bleep] in a windmill.
And guess what.
We did it a second time.
And my husband
would never say
what you've said to me.
- [sighs]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- What?
- Can I pray over you
before I leave?
- No.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- What I believe love is,
it's loving someone
unconditionally
and wholeheartedly.
If you love me,
then you love me
and you love
everything about me.
You know that
there's flaws about me,
but you love me
through those flaws.
That's what I want.
You're not gonna tell me what
I should and shouldn't do.
And that's the language
that he was using.
I answer to the Lord.
I don't answer to Luke.
I feel a weight
lifted off my shoulders
that, like,
I finally
figured it out for myself.
I'm just, like, relieved.
I never have to
deal with him again.
[intense music]
- Next week
on "The Bachelorette"...
- The Luke P. show's over,
boys.
- Dude.
- Oh, my God.
- Finally.
- I've never been so stoked
to see someone leave
in my life.
[laughter]
- With Luke
out of the picture,
it allows me to finally
look at my other relationships.
- We still have a Rose Ceremony
to go through,
but it's a good day.
[eerie off-key notes]
- Hannah thought
there's no way I'd want
to be with her anymore
after the last thing
she told me,
and...she's sadly mistaken.
[dramatic chords]
This isn't over for me yet.
This is my heart
we're talking about here.
- It's--
this is not about your heart.
[bleep]--leave!
- Why are you still here?
- She said no.
How many more "no's"
do you need?
- Lay your hands off me.
- Or what?
- Yeah, what are you gonna do?
- And then...
- ♪ All the other dudes
got me feeling so spressed ♪
♪ So I say all aboard,
hotness express ♪
Oh!
[crowd cheers]
- It's a very special
"Men Tell All"...
- You can honestly just go
[bleep] yourself, dude.
- When all the guys you've
loved this season return...
- Your story has changed.
- What did you say, dude?
Just what did you say?
- Including the guys
you love to hate.
- You're violent.
You're aggressive.
You are a psychopath.
- Karma is a bitch,
and you're gonna get yours.
- What will Luke do now?
- I've already given you
a piece of my heart.
But I hope in the future,
I can give you all of it.
- Find out next week.
And then, in two weeks...
- [bleep] me.
This is why you don't date
two people at the same time.
- It's an unbelievable
season finale...
- I can tell you have concerns.
So just--
will you just say 'em?
- When Hannah
faces the decision
that will change her life.
- This is really [bleep] up.
Now I'm freaking out.
- I want somebody
that will love you
like I know
you should be loved.
[dramatic music intensifies]
- It's all coming up
on "The Bachelorette."
- Fruit and chocolate cake,
Fantasy Suite with my girl:
Does it get any better
than this?
- Mmm.
- I don't think so.
All right, let's see
if we got any better.
- Oh, okay.
- You ready for this?
All right, three, two, one.
- [grunts]
- Oh, I thought we got it.
- I thought we did too.
- It, like, disappeared.
- Okay. Go again.
- All right, ready?
Two.
- God--
Peter, that was in my hair.
That was not--
- That was not in your hair.
- That was like right here.
- You're putting this
on me now?
Okay.
- I'm, like, over here.
Get into the light.
We gotta get this.
This is making me mad.
- I know.
[laughs]
- [bleep]!
- That was not my fault.
- Okay, do it again.
- [mimics plane droning]
- No, I want to--
I gotta get it.
- Three, two...
- Peter!
- It's--
you try throwing it.
Look--
look how it gets stuck
with the chocolate.
- [laughs]
- See?
It, like, veers off.
You can't put it straight.
- Let me try it again.
- We're gonna be here all
night.
- I will not go upstairs
unless--
- Until we get this
in the mouth.
- [gasps]
That one was--
- Hannah.
You put it in my shirt.
- [laughs]
- How did--
how did you do that?